Baylor-Carrington Family papers, Inclusive: 1715-2007, undated, Bulk: 1840-1930
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Photographic Materials, 1849-1941; 6
  - Baylor Family Reunions, 1930, 1932 July 4, 1939 July 3-4 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Family, 1929 August 28-1939 May (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Family (1 of 6), undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Family (2 of 6), undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Baylor Family (3 of 6), undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Baylor Family (4 of 6), undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Baylor Family (5 of 6), undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Baylor Family (6 of 6), undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Baylor Family (1 of 4), undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Negatives: Baylor Family (2 of 4), undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Negatives: Baylor Family (3 of 4), undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Negatives: Baylor Family (4 of 4), undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Carrington Family, circa 1889-1941 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Carrington Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Photo Albums: Josie Carrington (1 of 2), 1849-1939 February, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Photo Albums: Josie Carrington (2 of 2), 1849-1939 February, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Photo Albums: Mrs. D.W. Carrington, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: George Baylor Allen, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - James Drucilla Allen, circa 1897, 1928, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - James Drucilla Allen, undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Mayme R. and Bessie Allen, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Allen Family, 1864, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Artifacts, 1800-1939; 7
  This series consists of a variety of family heirloom artifacts, including spoons, fabric items, and the printing plate for a map of Baylor University campus.
  - Spoons: Addie Sue Carrington, 1937 May (Box [1071] OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Spoons: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor, circa 1880-1885 (Box [1071] OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Ear Muffs, undated (Box [1071] OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Clock Winder, undated (Box [1071] OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Bedspreads: Rachel Ewing Carrington, circa 1800 (Box 22 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Pillowcases: Florence Black Baylor, 1897 (Box 22 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Doilies: Lucy Waytt, circa 1890 (Box 22 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Silk Purse, undated (Box 22 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Aprons: Emily “Emy” Jane Hanna Baylor, undated (Box 22 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Printing Plate: Baylor Campus Map, 1939 (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 2)
- Scrapbooks, 1816-1949; 8
  This series consists of an album of poetry and pictures, an autograph book, and several scrapbooks. There are scrapbooks of the Civil War, WWI, and a Baylor family reunion. The scrapbooks include correspondence, newspaper clippings, and photographs.
  Photographic print
  - Scrapbook 1: Album of Poetry and Pictures, 1816-1847 January 30, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook 1: Album of Poetry and Pictures: Loose Items (1 of 2), 1816-1847 January 30, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook 1: Album of Poetry and Pictures: Loose Items (2 of 2), 1816-1847 January 30, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (1 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (2 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (3 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (4 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (5 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (6 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (7 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (8 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook 2: Civil War (9 of 9), 1859 March 12-1879 August, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor (1 of 8), 1861 May 30-1939 June 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor (2 of 8), 1861 May 30-1939 June 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor (3 of 8), 1861 May 30-1939 June 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor (4 of 8), 1861 May 30-1939 June 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor (5 of 8), 1861 May 30-1939 June 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor (6 of 8), 1861 May 30-1939 June 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor (7 of 8), 1861 May 30-1939 June 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor (8 of 8), 1861 May 30-1939 June 20, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook 3: George Wythe Baylor, undated (Box [1068] OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Scrapbook 4: Autograph Book: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (1 of 7), 1873 March 5-1880 July 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook 4: Autograph Book: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (2 of 7), 1873 March 5-1880 July 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook 4: Autograph Book: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (3 of 7), 1873 March 5-1880 July 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook 4: Autograph Book: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (4 of 7), 1873 March 5-1880 July 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook 4: Autograph Book: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (5 of 7), 1873 March 5-1880 July 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook 4: Autograph Book: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (6 of 7), 1873 March 5-1880 July 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook 4: Autograph Book: Addie DeLeon Hamer Baylor (7 of 7), 1873 March 5-1880 July 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Scrapbook 5 (1 of 2), 1896 April-1897 August 12, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook 5 (2 of 2), 1896 April-1897 August 12, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Scrapbook 6: Addie Baylor Carrington, 1914 June (Box 20 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (1 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (2 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (3 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (4 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (5 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (6 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (7 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (8 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (9 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (10 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (11 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (12 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (13 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (14 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (15 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (16 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (17 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (18 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (19 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (20 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (21 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (22 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (23 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor (24 of 24), 1916 December-1921 August 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook 7: World War I: John Roy Baylor: Loose Items, 1927 October 21, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook 8: World War I: John Roy Baylor (1 of 5), 1907 May 24-1919 March 30, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook 8: World War I: John Roy Baylor (2 of 5), 1907 May 24-1919 March 30, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook 8: World War I: John Roy Baylor (3 of 5), 1907 May 24-1919 March 30, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook 8: World War I: John Roy Baylor (4 of 5), 1907 May 24-1919 March 30, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook 8: World War I: John Roy Baylor (5 of 5), 1907 May 24-1919 March 30, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbook 9: Baylor Family Reunion and Death of Samuel Palmer Brooks (1 of 7), 1929 December-1931 May 28, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Scrapbook 9: Baylor Family Reunion and Death of Samuel Palmer Brooks (2 of 7), 1929 December-1931 May 28, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook 9: Baylor Family Reunion and Death of Samuel Palmer Brooks (3 of 7), 1929 December-1931 May 28, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Scrapbook 9: Baylor Family Reunion and Death of Samuel Palmer Brooks (4 of 7), 1929 December-1931 May 28, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Scrapbook 9: Baylor Family Reunion and Death of Samuel Palmer Brooks (5 of 7), 1929 December-1931 May 28, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Scrapbook 9: Baylor Family Reunion and Death of Samuel Palmer Brooks (6 of 7), 1929 December-1931 May 28, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbook 9: Baylor Family Reunion and Death of Samuel Palmer Brooks (7 of 7), 1929 December-1931 May 28, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Scrapbook 10: Autograph Book (1 of 4), 1938 April 30-1949 August 15 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Scrapbook 10: Autograph Book (2 of 4), 1938 April 30-1949 August 15 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Scrapbook 10: Autograph Book (3 of 4), 1938 April 30-1949 August 15 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Scrapbook 10: Autograph Book (4 of 4), 1938 April 30-1949 August 15 (Box 18, Folder 32)